Guide to the National Council of Jewish Women, Pittsburgh Section Records, 1894-2011 AIS.1964.40
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- NCJW Oral History Projects, 1967-2001; XXVIII.
  - Pittsburgh Section Project II: My Voice was Heard, 2.
    - Klionsky, Bernard, Dr., 1989 (Box 103, Folder 30)
    - Kochin, Louis, undated; No folder exists. (Box 103, Folder 30A)
    - Koerner, Henry, December 1978 (Box 103, Folder 31)
    - Koss, David, 1984 (Box 103, Folder 32)
    - Kranich, Joel, 1997 (Box 103, Folder 33)
    - Krause, Corinne Azen, 1997 (Box 103, Folder 34)
    - Kreimer, Hilda R., 1999 (Box 103, Folder 35)
    - Kurtzman, David H., Dr., 1975 (Box 103, Folder 36)
    - Kwalwasser, Edgar, 1992 (Box 103, Folder 37)
    - Labovitz, Gertrude, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 38)
    - Landes, Morris, 1990 (Box 103, Folder 39)
    - Lapiduss, Esther, 1987 (Box 103, Folder 40)
    - Lasday, Harry, 1983 (Box 103, Folder 41)
    - Latterman, Marilyn, December 3, 1997 (Box 103, Folder 42)
    - Lavine, Shirley, 1985 (Box 103, Folder 43)
    - Lehman, Vivian, February 3, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 44)
    - Levin, Stanley H., July 26, 1982 (Box 103, Folder 45)
    - Levine, Ezra, March 18, 1991 (Box 103, Folder 46)
    - Levine, Mike, 1991 (Box 103, Folder 47)
    - Levinson, Aaron P., June 20, 1977 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Levinson, Harriet Dorfan, January 21, 1998 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Levinson, Julian P., Dr., July 7, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Levinson, Rose, May 4, 1977 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Lewenstein, Minnie, February 7, 1992 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Libson, Margaret, March 18, 1976 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Lieber, Ruth W., May 26, 1995 (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Light, Elaine Kahn, June 9, 1992 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Light, Ernest, February 9, 1998 (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Litman, Anne, 1982 (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Litman, Lenny, January 14, 1987 (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - Litman, Roslyn, March 6, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - Livingston, Ruth, June 16, 1986 (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - Lopatin, Anita, May 14, 1985 (Box 104, Folder 14)
    - Lowenthal, Anne, December 9, 1981 (Box 104, Folder 15)
    - Lowenthal, Alexander (Alex), January 22, 1978; May 22, 1988 (Box 104, Folder 16)
    - Lyon, Molly, January 23, 1976 (Box 104, Folder 17)
    - Maazel, Lincoln, November 11, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 18)
    - Maazel, Marion (Marie), 1974 (Box 104, Folder 19)
    - Marcus, Florence, July 22, 1992 (Box 104, Folder 20)
    - Marcus, Jacob Rader, Dr., May 9, 1979 (Box 104, Folder 21)
    - Margolis, Harry M., Dr., April 24, 1991 (Box 104, Folder 22)
    - Markovic, Malvina, August 18, 1999 (Box 104, Folder 23)
    - Masloff, Sophie (Box 104, Folder 24)
      - Masloff, Sophie, August 10, 1987
      - Masloff, Sophie, April 22, 1994
    - Melamed, Nathan T., February 18, 1998 (Box 104, Folder 25)
    - Meltzer, Allen, August 8, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 26)
    - Menlowe, Mildred, December 1, 1976 (Box 104, Folder 27)
    - Mermelstein, Howard, Dr., November 15, 1990 (Box 104, Folder 28)
    - Meyer, Irma, March 11, 1987 (Box 104, Folder 29)
    - Meyers, Sophia, March 2, 1982 (Box 104, Folder 30)
    - Meyerson, Erma T., August 1991 (Box 104, Folder 31)
    - Michaels, Edgar W., March 20, 1992 (Box 104, Folder 32)
    - Michaels, Lois G., April 15, 1999 (Box 104, Folder 33)
    - Milch, Pauline, December 19, 1977 (Box 104, Folder 34)
    - Miller, Roland, November 20, 1991 (Box 104, Folder 35)
    - Mintz, Ida, March 10, 1982 (Box 104, Folder 36)
    - Morganstern, Anita, 1977 (Box 104, Folder 37)
    - Moritz, Donald, October 24, 1996 (Box 104, Folder 38)
    - Morris, Jack., August 4, 1989 (Box 104, Folder 39)
    - Needleman, Herbert L., Dr., January 3, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 40)
    - Nelkin, Arthur, May 19, 1986 (Box 104, Folder 41)
    - Notov, Ida, March 23, 1987 (Box 104, Folder 42)
    - Noven, Samuel J., March 27, 1978 (Box 104, Folder 43)
    - Novick, Ivan J. (Box 104, Folder 44)
      - Novick, Ivan J., December 1, 1997
      - Novick, Ivan J., 1998
    - Ohringer, Helen, 1985 (Box 104, Folder 45)
    - Oppenheimer, Asher, December 9, 1987 (Box 104, Folder 46)
    - Oseroff, Pauline, October 28, 1975 (Box 104, Folder 47)
    - Ostrow, Gerald, July 6, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 48)
    - Palkovitz, Judith L., April 5, 2000 (Box 104, Folder 49)
    - Paradise, Leone, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 50)
    - Parker, Meyer, October 30, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 51)
    - Paris, Barry, June 18, 1998 (Box 104, Folder 52)
    - Passamaneck, Herman, June 1976 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Pearl, Fanny (Box 105, Folder 2)
      - Pearl, Fanny, undated
      - Pearl, Fanny, 1984
    - Perlman, Mark, February 6, 1996 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Perlow, Benjamin, 1983 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Pois, Joseph, Dr., December 12, 1984 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Porter, Milton, January 27, 1976 (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Porter, Rachel, May 24, 1990 (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - Posner, Henry Jr., October 1, 1994 (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - Posner, Ida, February 5, 1985 (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - Posner, Sholom, 1974 (Box 105, Folder 10)
    - Poupko, Rabbi Bernard A. (Baruch), July 26, 1976 (Box 105, Folder 11)
    - Preisser, Bernice, March 26, 1987 (Box 105, Folder 12)
    - Raizman, Albert, February 14, 1991 (Box 105, Folder 13)
    - Raphael, Israel (J.R.), January 20, 1976 (Box 105, Folder 14)
    - Rauh, Richard E., 1994, 1998 (Box 105, Folder 15)
    - Reinard, Frieda, May 7, 1981 (Box 105, Folder 16)
    - Reizenstein, Louis, July 24, 1974 (Box 105, Folder 17)
    - Richman, Hyman, July 11, 1986 (Box 105, Folder 18)
    - Rider, Sam, March 19, 1996 (Box 105, Folder 19)
    - Robin, John G., February 1981 (Box 105, Folder 20)
    - Robinson, Donald (Box 105, Folder 21)
      - Robinson, Donald, January 27, 1978
      - Robinson, Donald, November 28, 1994
    - Robinson, Sylvia, August 12, 1996 (Box 105, Folder 22)
    - Rogal, Alvin, 1995 (Box 105, Folder 23)
    - Rogal, Hyman., undated (Box 105, Folder 24)
    - Rogal, Martha, May 7, 1975 (Box 105, Folder 25)
    - Rosen, Benjamin, July 6, 1985 (Box 105, Folder 26)
    - Rosen, Seymour, April 14, 1976 (Box 105, Folder 27)
    - Rosenbaum, Stanley, January 27, 1987 (Box 105, Folder 28)
    - Rosenberg, Charlotte, January 1976 (Box 105, Folder 29)
    - Rosenberg, Jacob (Jock), 1984 (Box 105, Folder 30)
    - Rosenberg, Jerome Laib, Dr., May 1, 1988 (Box 105, Folder 31)
    - Rosenberg, Libbie, November 13, 1983 (Box 105, Folder 32)
    - Rosensweet, Alvin, October 6, 1986 (Box 105, Folder 33)
    - Rosenthal, Libbie, May 19, 1978 (Box 105, Folder 34)
    - Roskies, Ralph, December 19, 1996 (Box 105, Folder 35)
    - Ruslander, Julian, October 20, 1977 (Box 105, Folder 36)
    - Roth, Audrey, March 6, 1996 (Box 105, Folder 37)
    - Ruben, Sol H., 1998 (Box 105, Folder 38)
    - Rubenstein, Joseph, May 17, 1996 (Box 105, Folder 39)
    - Rudolph, Leonard, 1996 (Box 105, Folder 40)
    - Ruttenberg, Harold, February 24, 1986 (Box 105, Folder 41)
    - Ruttenberg, Katherine M. (Kitty) (Box 105, Folder 42)
      - Ruttenberg, Katherine M. (Kitty), 1985
      - Ruttenberg, Katherine M. (Kitty), January 30, 1992
    - Sacks, Aaron, November 7, 1990 (Box 105, Folder 43)
    - Sacks, Gussie Miller, May 12, 1976 (Box 105, Folder 44)
    - Sajowitz, William, Rabbi, 1985 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Saul, Joseph, 1985 (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Saul, Sidney, Dr., September 1981 (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Schienholtz, Leonard, October 30, 1998 (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Schmidt, Sally, 1984 (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Schuster, Elizabeth, 1984 (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Schwartz, Fanny Hart, March 6, 1982 (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - Schwarz, Frank, December 11, 1986 (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - Schwartz, Leonard, Dr., September 24, 1992 (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - Schwartz, Nathan, Dr., January 1993 (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - Seidenberg, Melvin, January 22, 1990 (Box 106, Folder 11)
    - Selznick, Milton, June 23, 1997 (Box 106, Folder 12)
    - Shapira, Frieda (Box 106, Folder 13)
      - Shapira, Frieda, 1979
      - Shapira, Frieda, 1992
    - Shapiro, Belle, 1987 (Box 106, Folder 14)
    - Shapiro, Charlotte, Dr., August 1988 (Box 106, Folder 15)
    - Shapiro, Joseph, June 11, 1974 (Box 106, Folder 16)
    - Shapiro, Maurice A., August 10, 1990 (Box 106, Folder 17)
    - Shapiro, Sam, 1988 (Box 106, Folder 18)
    - Shapiro, Zalman M. (Zalmon Mordecai) (Box 106, Folder 19)
      - Shapiro, Zalman M. (Zalmon Mordecai), August 1984
      - Shapiro, Zalman M. (Zalmon Mordecai), June 8, 1994
    - Shore, Barbara K., January 27, 1993 (Box 106, Folder 20)
    - Shore, Gussie, May 8, 1986 (Box 106, Folder 21)
    - Siegal, Fritz, May 1987 (Box 106, Folder 22)
    - Silberman, Freda, February 1, 1996 (Box 106, Folder 23)
    - Silberman, Marianne, March 1, 1983 (Box 106, Folder 24)
    - Silverblatt, Rose Middleman, August 8, 1989 (Box 106, Folder 25)
    - Simon, Betty Ann (Goodman), May 18, 1989 (Box 106, Folder 26)
    - Skirboll, Leonard, May 7, 1997 (Box 106, Folder 27)
    - Sklar, Morris, 1990 (Box 106, Folder 28)
    - Slesinger, George, 1969 (Box 106, Folder 29)
    - Slesinger, Reuben E., 1986 (Box 106, Folder 30)
    - Slomberg, Leah, 1998 (Box 106, Folder 31)
    - Snyder, Herman, 1993 (Box 106, Folder 32)
    - Snyderman, William, undated (Box 106, Folder 33)
    - Soroker, Gerald, 1993 (Box 106, Folder 34)
    - Speyer, Tillie, 1976 (Box 106, Folder 35)
    - Spirer, Helen, 1986 (Box 106, Folder 36)
    - Stark, Sadie, 1973 (Box 106, Folder 37)
    - Stark, William, 1991, 1992, 1997 (Box 106, Folder 38)
    - Steinfeld, Betty, May 6, 1997 (Box 106, Folder 39)
    - Steinfeld, Eddie, February 20, 1984 (Box 106, Folder 40)
    - Stern, Mark, March 17, 1986 (Box 106, Folder 41)
    - Stock, Belle, November 20, 1995 (Box 106, Folder 42)
    - Strassberger, Eugene, Sr., December 6, 1974 (Box 106, Folder 43)
    - Strauss, Samuel, Judge, April 10, 1984 (Box 106, Folder 44)
    - Susman, Milton, November 10, 1976 (Box 106, Folder 45)
    - Susman, Minnie, 1975 (Box 106, Folder 46)
    - Taube, Moshe, November 22, 1994 (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Thorpe, Harvey, December 20, 1977 (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - Tisherman, Sam, Dr., May 1998 (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Titlebaum, Jacob (Jake), May 31, 1981 (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Topolsky, Bess, 1987 (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Twerski, Abraham J., 1988 (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Vatz, Virginia H., 1994 (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Verman, Sam, November 2, 1988 (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Vixman, Rachel, October 20, 1977 (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - Wald, Neil, Dr., September 13, 1993 (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - Wechsler, Harry, February 4, 1982 (Box 107, Folder 11)
    - Wechsler, Sylvia, October 17, 1977 (Box 107, Folder 12)
    - Wecht, Cyril H., 1996 (Box 107, Folder 13)
    - Weil, Andrew L., 1995 (Box 107, Folder 14)
    - Weinberg, Jacob L. (Jake), 1993 (Box 107, Folder 15)
    - Weiner, Margery, 1988 (Box 107, Folder 16)
    - Weisberg, Saul, May 31, 1985 (Box 107, Folder 17)
    - Weiss, Milton G., February 13, 1991 (Box 107, Folder 18)
    - Weitzman, Leonard, November 29, 1990 (Box 107, Folder 19)
    - Wekselman, Martin, Judge, March 15, 1989 (Box 107, Folder 20)
    - Wender, Dr. Irving, W., March 3, 1996 (Box 107, Folder 21)
    - Wertheimer, Herbert G., May 9, 1997 (Box 107, Folder 22)
    - Winograd, Bess, March 19, 1974 (Box 107, Folder 23)
    - Winograd, Leonard, Rabbi, January 26, 1982 (Box 107, Folder 24)
    - Wolf, John M., June 15, 1995 (Box 107, Folder 25)
    - Wolfson, Marty, November 29, 1990 (Box 107, Folder 26)
    - Wolfson, Miriam, November 5, 1975 (Box 107, Folder 27)
    - Wolk, Abraham L. (Abe), Judge, February 1982 (Box 107, Folder 28)
    - Yecies, Gizella, May 17, 1991 (Box 107, Folder 29)
    - Younger, Julius, December 2, 1992 (Box 107, Folder 30)
    - Zecher, Albert D., January 27, 1994 (Box 107, Folder 31)
    - Zelkowitz, Milton, February 25, 2000 (Box 107, Folder 32)
    - Zoffer, H. Jerome (Jerry), January 22, 1993 (Box 107, Folder 33)
    - Zytnick, Allan, July 25, 1997 (Box 107, Folder 34)
    - New Material Added, 2011
      - Information and notes compiled by Minnie Susman and Sara Lefkowitz, 1974-1975 (Box 114, Folder 19)
      - Ida Cohen Selavan Oral History Project II contract, 1977-1979 (Box 114, Folder 20)
      - Oral History Project Summaries, Fact Sheets, and Methodologies, 1977-2011 (Box 114, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence with Potential Respondents, 1978 (Box 114, Folder 22)
      - Oral History Project II Information, 1978 (Box 114, Folder 23)
      - My Voice was Heard materials sent to publisher, 1978 (Box 114, Folder 24)
      - Oral History Project II Newspaper clippings, 1978-1982 (Box 114, Folder 25)
      - Angel, Francis, ca. 1980s (Box 114, Folder 26)
      - My Voice was Heard chapter lay-out with editorial marks, ca. 1980 (Box 114, Folder 27)
      - My Voice was Heard Reception, November 23, 1980 (Box 114, Folder 28)
      - List of gift shops, synagogue gift shops, and religious schools selling My voice was Heard, 1980-1981 (Box 114, Folder 29)
      - Oral History Project II Funding, 1980, 1985 (Box 114, Folder 30)
      - My Voice was Heard Marketing Committee, 1980-1982 (Box 114, Folder 31)
      - KTAV Publishing House price quote for My Voice was Heard, 1980 (Box 114, Folder 32)
      - History and Marketing of "Bridges to History", 1980-1990 (Box 114, Folder 33)
      - Publicity Promotions for Radio, Television, and Press, 1980-1981 (Box 114, Folder 34)
      - List of Bookstores selling My Voice as Heard, 1980-1981 (Box 114, Folder 35)
      - Interviewers and Respondents Follow-ups, 1981-1983 (Box 114, Folder 36)
      - Correspondence, 1981, 1984 (Box 114, Folder 36)
      - Oral History Project II Grants, 1981-1982 (Box 114, Folder 37)
      - My Voice was Heard correspondence and orders, 1981, 1985 (Box 114, Folder 38)
      - My Voice was Heard Book Reviews, 1982 (Box 114, Folder 39)
      - Presentations on the Oral History Projects, 1982-1985 (Box 114, Folder 40)
      - Oral History Project Events and Book Sales, 1983-1986 (Box 114, Folder 41)
      - Respondents and Interviewers Assignments, 1984-1988 (Box 114, Folder 42)
      - My Voice was Heard Marketing and Sales Report, 1985-1986 (Box 114, Folder 43)
      - List of Respondents and Interviewers, 1988-1993 (Box 114, Folder 44)
      - Columbus Day Celebrations Grants, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 45)
      - Access to an Oral History Collection: The Jewish Experience in Pittsburgh Galley Sheets, 1991 (Box 114, Folder 46)
      - Pennsylvania Historical and Museum Commission Survey of Oral History Collections Profile, 1992 (Box 114, Folder 47)
      - Balance of Budgeted Amount for Expenses from Blumenthal Fund, 1992-1993 (Box 114, Folder 48)
      - Oral History Project II Newspaper clippings, 1992-2001 (Box 114, Folder 49)
      - Oral History Association Meeting Session Proposals, 1993-1996 (Box 114, Folder 50)
      - Funding Contributions Thank You Letters, 1993-2002 (Box 114, Folder 51)
      - List of Libraries that copies of the guide Pittsburgh and Beyond were distributed, 1993 (Box 114, Folder 52)
      - Correspondence with Respondents, 1993-1999 (Box 114, Folder 53)
      - Oral History Association Information, 1992-1999 (Box 114, Folder 54)
      - Pittsburgh and Beyond Correspondence and Orders, 1994-1997 (Box 114, Folder 55)
      - My Voice was Heard and Pittsburgh & Beyond Libraries Distribution List, 1994-2001 (Box 114, Folder 56)
      - Requests for My Voice was Heard and Pittsburgh and Beyond, 1995-2002 (Box 114, Folder 57)
      - "Bridges to the Future" sound bites., 1996 (Box 117, Cassette 1-9)
      - Oral History Project Birthday Celebration Flyers, 1996, 1998 (Box 114, Folder 58)
      - Oral History Association Meeting Panel Proposal, 1996 (Box 114, Folder 59)
      - "History of the Oral History Project," by Marlene Haus, 1997 (Box 114, Folder 60)
      - "Bridges to the Future" Press Release and Premiere Flyer, 1997 (Box 114, Folder 61)
      - Oral History Project Website Development with Arundel Consulting, 1997-1998 (Box 114, Folder 62)
      - List of Completed Interviews as of February 1, 1998, 1997-1998 (Box 114, Folder 63)
      - Oral History Project Funding, 1998-1999 (Box 114, Folder 64)
      - Release for Oral History Materials for Russian Wedding Documentary, 1999 (Box 114, Folder 65)
      - Partners in Creation and My Voice was Heard Hebrew Translation Changes, 2000 (Box 114, Folder 66)
      - "An Evening in Paris: Celebrating the NCJW's Oral History Project", 2000 (Box 114, Folder 67)
      - Pittsburgh and Beyond Fan Mail, 2002 (Box 114, Folder 68)
      - NCJW Pittsburgh Section Bulletin with updates on the Oral History Project, 2006-2007 (Box 114, Folder 69)
      - Order Forms for My Voice was Heard and Pittsburgh and Beyond, undated (Box 114, Folder 70)
  - South Hills Branch Oral History Project, 3.
    The South Hills branch of NCJW collected nineteen interviews from Jewish residents of Pittsburgh, concentrating primarily on their immigration experiences and early lives in Western Pennsylvania. Although these interviews cover subjects similar to those of the Pittsburgh Section projects, they are not part of the same study. Files contain questionnaires, descriptions of the interviewees' homes, abstracts, and photographs.
    - Staff Guidelines for Access (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Americus, Norman (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Ballon, Rebecca (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Bendis, Mildred (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Cohen, Helen (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Cooper, Charlotte (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - Freed, Marilyn (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - Hirsh, Harold (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - Joseph, Goldie (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - Korn, Fannie (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - Leventon, Alice (Box 108, Folder 11)
    - Lipman, Saul S. (Box 108, Folder 12)
    - Miller, Izzy (Box 108, Folder 13)
    - Miller, Max (Box 108, Folder 14)
    - Miller, Pincus F. (Box 108, Folder 15)
    - Roth, Stanley (Box 108, Folder 16)
    - Rubenstein, David (Box 108, Folder 17)
    - Schlansky, Clara (Box 108, Folder 18)
    - Wilk, Morris (Box 108, Folder 19)
    - Wittlin, Edward (Box 108, Folder 20)
  - Advisory Committee, 1971-2011; 4.
    The Advisory Committee began as the Oral Jewish History Committee. The committee's role was to supervise all aspects of the oral histroy project from the selection of respondents, recruitment of voulnteers, seeking publication, and directing the future uses of the project. The subseries contains information from both phases of the project and includes notes on suggested oral history respondents and the project as it developed. The files in this subseries date from 1971 to 2011 and are arranged chronologically.
    - Meeting Minutes, 1971-1975 (Box 114, Folder 71)
    - Meeting Agendas, 1973 (Box 114, Folder 72)
    - Oral History Interviews statuses within the year, 1974-1999 (Box 114, Folder 73)
    - Correspondence, 1975-2005 (Box 114, Folder 74)
    - Oral History Project Progress and Annual Reports, 1975-1980 (Box 114, Folder 75)
    - Meeting on Oral History Project II, 1975 (Box 114, Folder 76)
    - Meeting Materials, 1975-1976 (Box 114, Folder 77)
    - Correspondence and Memos with the University of Pitttsburgh Library System and Archives Service Center, 1977-2000 (Box 114, Folder 78)
    - Meeting Agendas, Reports, and Minutes, 1980-1986 (Box 114, Folder 79)
    - Notes and Worksheets, 1980-1987 (Box 114, Folder 80)
    - Annual Reports, 1981-1984 (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Meeting Minutes, Notes, Reports, and Lists, 1981-1984 (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Meetings and Notes, 1984-1986 (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence with the Archives Service Center, 1984, 1990-2002 (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Meeting Notes and Worksheets, 1988-1993 (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Meeting Agendas and Reports, 1993 (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - Selected and Suggested Oral History Respondents, 1993-1994 (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - Committee Notes, 1993, 2002 (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - Computers and Software Memo, 1994 (Box 115, Folder 9)
    - Reports from Oral History Project Chairmen, 1992, 1994-1995 (Box 115, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1994, 2001 (Box 115, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence with Dr. Peter Stearns regarding Oral History Project and Carnegie-Mellon University, 1994 (Box 115, Folder 12)
    - Meeting Minutes, January- December 1995 (Box 115, Folder 13)
    - Committee Notes, 1996 (Box 115, Folder 14)
    - Meeting Announcements, 1996-1997 (Box 115, Folder 15)
    - Meeting Minutes, January- December 1996 (Box 115, Folder 16)
    - Meeting Minutes, January- December 1997 (Box 115, Folder 17)
    - Committee Notes, 1997 (Box 115, Folder 18)
    - United Jewish Federation Pilot Project, 1997, 1999 (Box 115, Folder 19)
    - Advisory Committee Member, Marcia Frumerman Biographical Information, 1997 (Box 115, Folder 20)
    - Meeting Minutes, January- December 1998 (Box 115, Folder 21)
    - Suggested Respondents, 1998-2000 (Box 115, Folder 22)
    - Meeting Minutes, January- December 1999 (Box 115, Folder 23)
    - Meeting Minutes, January- August 2000 (Box 115, Folder 24)
    - Discussion with the Archives Service Center regarding Oral History Website, 2000 (Box 115, Folder 25)
    - Meetings Materials and Reports, 1999, 2001-2002 (Box 115, Folder 26)
    - Meeting Minutes, April 29, 2008 (Box 115, Folder 27)
    - Oral History Project Timeline and Achievements, 2010-2011 (Box 115, Folder 28)
  - Oral History Course Curriculum Development, 1989-2007; 5.
    This subseries includes material from the creation of adult continuing education courses on Jewish history and identity which were developed from the oral history interviews. The Oral History Course Curriculum Development subseries contain materials from 1975 to 2000 and is arranged chronologically.
    - "Roots of Jewish Values" Course Materials, 1989 (Box 115, Folder 29)
    - Proposal for Oral History Course Curriculum Development, 1997-1998 (Box 115, Folder 30)
    - Curriculum Development Funding, 1997-1999 (Box 115, Folder 31)
    - "Living Judaism" Course Materials and Syllabus, 1998 (Box 115, Folder 32)
    - "Living Judaism" Course Development, 1998-1999 (Box 115, Folder 33)
    - Curriculum Development Committee Meeting Minutes, 1998-1999 (Box 115, Folder 34)
    - Nathan Cumming Foundation Grant Request, 1998-1999 (Box 115, Folder 35)
    - United Jewish Federation Curriculum Development Grant, 1999 (Box 115, Folder 36)
    - "History of Jewish Pittsburgh" Course Development, 1999 (Box 115, Folder 37)
    - Curriculum Consultants Invoices, 1999 (Box 115, Folder 38)
    - Covenant Foundation Grant Request, 1999 (Box 115, Folder 39)
    - "History of Jewish Pittsburgh" Course Materials, 2000 (Box 115, Folder 40)
    - Magic Lantern Company, Oral History Course Teaching Aids Zip disc, 2001 (Box 115, Folder 41)
    - Correspondence and Notes regarding Carnegie-Mellon University course Language In Design student projects, 2001 (Box 115, Folder 42)
    - Correspondence regarding Design of Oral History Course Teaching Aid by Language In Design Students, 2001 (Box 115, Folder 43)
    - "Language In Design:" Interview Excerpts used in Class Presentation CD-ROM, 2001 (Box 115, Folder 44)
    - "Language In Design:" Student Project NCJW Session One CD-ROM, 2001 (Box 115, Folder 45)
    - "Language In Design:" Student Project, family Tree Teaching Aid CD-ROM, 2001 (Box 115, Folder 46)
    - "Language In Design:" Daniel Wood and Camellia George Designed Teaching Aids CD-ROM, 2001 (Box 115, Folder 47)
    - "Language In Design:" Student Presentations VHS, 2001 (Box 115, Folder 48)
    - "Language In Design:" Student Projects, 2001 (Box 115, Folder 49)
    - Oral History Interview Excerpts to be used in Course Development, 2001 (Box 115, Folder 50)
    - "In Their Own Words: An Oral History of Jewish Pittsburgh" Pilot Program Course Materials, 2001-2002 (Box 115, Folder 51)